25 feet which is motivating you now
see if you are working in the office then if you
leave it then there is permanent motivation
but your motivational level right now should be near
leaving these five minutes,
after watching the video your motivation level will increase let's
start the video a
little number one happy teachers day gift there is
no side effect in the world for doing any work your condition
job this in which situations you need this is the right
time to start any work
what we think that our feelings will
come when we start that work but the
digit is that right now your feelings are
subscribe now they will go away in the coming time
if you have started waiting like this then do
n't wait for what this
time is going on right here whatever you want to do then
start with the person with whom you want to do it no the second remedy saloni
distraction addictions it is not your fault that you are
dating that person or it is your fault that you are
finally returning to
call him I am asking you  No question, the
level of motivation increases
when we do any solution well,
finish any work, only then
we get motivation to
study that is at a fixed rate for example, make your goal to study for two-three
hours and if you achieve this goal,
your motivation will increase, now how will you do it
and on the other hand, if you
leave your work midway, for example, you started
watching TV with the mobile channel on
or went out for a walk, that is, you
left your work midway, then the work will
not be completed, then its notification will come and then it will
decrease and the waste will decrease, so
whenever you study or do any work, do not
ignore the distraction to delete it,
now a little son, compare
yourself with others,
Bill Gates once said that do not compare yourself with anyone else, do not
compare yourself
with anyone in this process and if you do
so, then you will lose your self  We are insulting, that is,
some who grow old due to accidents
and in some things we are better than our friends,
so the names are complete,
like us, these very good deeds, like these
we are modern in the whole world, I am
also unique, that is, you will not find a person like me
anywhere in this world and you will
also not find a person like you anywhere in this whole world,
what happens is that we do
less than wounds, so 30% of the time
we exaggerate ourselves in front of
others, at that time we
make ourselves look good, that is, we are happy and
can do it, but 70% of the time we
consider ourselves better than 200 and at that time we go into
depression,
now I am reading this recently
posted comparison support vein
make you better not peter compressor, do this at
home where you are becoming better,
some people are such that they do not have any work, they are completely
like candidates, they are
human beings, those people should compare themselves
with the sources which keep on reading  There is a
wonderful condition in the nerves, I
compete but I
compete to catch my mistakes so that I
work on those mistakes and
can make a better one, so keep in mind,
support benefits make you better, now the
fourth son, Chandigarh Singh means
creation and when you search on Google what
is the meaning of junk food, write stress, it will appear, I will
send the description link below, now you can
go to the set and read it, the food which has a lot of
calories, a lot of fat, is a
little sugar and the food
which has very less inos, very less
fiber, very less vitamins is
called junk food, whatever we
eat plays a big role on
our channel motivation, so when you see Azaan foot,
one thing should come out of your mind, there is
notification for admission, read this test,
see, put a
phone on the work, you feel that I cannot do that work,
some fast and the work which you have
everything in you to do, keep it in your heart that I
can do it, even if you have started it,
then do not give up on it that  I cannot do this, I
listened to this very carefully that
all the work in this world which is
practically possible, then if you have the
ability to do that work, nothing in this world is
impossible for you, a
new town near schedules, nothing is
impossible in this world, believe in it and make the
impossible possible, friends, I hope
you liked this video, so
quickly like this video and if you have
not subscribed to the channel yet, then do
subscribe and if you have
not followed it, then there is this question,
you have clicked on it, go there and definitely take this photo, so we will meet
in the next video, thank you.